a couple years ago in one of the
Transmissions you responded to a
question about gravity yes the copper
ball experiment yes in the copper ball
experiment it was a demonstration of
this notion that location is a property
of every object correct
I've been thinking about that every day
since oh all right and I want to talk
about some ideas that it came out of it
by all means but first I want to review
the experiments so that all of us can do
this together is that is that all right
yes the experiment is this idea many of
you already understand how our ships
travel from star to star because we
treat the idea of location as not a
place an object exists in but as an
actual equational vibrational property
of the object so that an object existing
here
and then existing here are actually
literally two different objects because
when you change the locational variable
in the object here and impose upon it
the idea of the energy of the locational
variable of this location the object
must by definition cease to exist here
and immediately and instantly exist here
and thus no travel in the intervening
distance has actually occurred the
object has simply popped out of one
reality and pop back into the reality
somewhere else based on the new
locational variable that you have
injected into its overall vibrational
signature equation so the experiment to
begin to practice this to learn this
principle is to have a very very flat
table very flat as flat as you can get
it and at least six to ten of your feet
long and have a very very thin as round
as you can make it thin copper fear
then you have the ability to extract
from that sphere either by striking it
or through some other methodology the
actual tone the signature frequency of
that pure very thin shelled copper
sphere that is hollow when you extract
the tone that is the signature frequency
of that sphere
and then move the sphere to the other
end of the table and extract the tone
from the sphere there location B then
move the sphere back to location a then
in any way you can with your technology
either acoustically or electronically
amplify and magnify the vibrational tone
of location B but bombard the sphere in
location a with the vibrational tone of
location B and you will begin to watch
that the sphere will start to roll to
location B automatically with that
vibrational tone and once it arrives in
that location we'll stop go no further
because it has found its resting Point
within that vibrational equation that's
the experiment
fascinating that will begin the ability
to investigate how to really unlock an
object from one vibration locational
reality and in that unlocked State
impose upon it enough energy of the new
location to have it actually pop out
from location a and pop in application B
without actually just traveling from one
point to the other
make sense yes all right what really
stuck out with me was the idea that it
traveled slowly and it made me wonder
about gravity in general yes
if first of all there's two things that
emerge from this experiment number one
if a vibration can be detected it must
be radiating from every object of course
that means that the location of all
objects the universe radiate their
location of course that's how we create
the navigational charts that our ships
use to go from place to place because
once you understand the Matrix of
locational vibrations in a relatively
limited area It's relatively easy to
extrapolate that out to the rest of the
universe right I assume there's a
graduation of frequency that relates to
location yes it's turning the entire
universe into the understanding of a
rheostat right
the other the emergent idea that comes
to experiment is that objects will take
on frequency and thus move to the
location representative of that
frequency yes
because in
it location I understand
isn't that exactly what gravity does I
mean right now our scientists talk about
gravity in terms of warping space and
lessons and innocent from one
perspective that isn't incorrect but
it's not the whole picture you're still
seeing just the side effect of the
relationship right of frequencies with
each other and the relationship of
geometry with itself in certain patterns
like let's take a massful object like a
neutron star highly dense collection of
men yeah it has a highly coherent
gravity wave radiation because there's a
lot of matter in one area yes that
radiates out and any object in its
vicinity takes on that frequency and and
as such it it's drawn in yes so that's
the mechanism of gravity isn't it yes
re-identifying the locational variables
within objects because it is powerful
enough to do so right
overwhelm the idea of their initial
locational signature and the objects
around like a Sun or a star or whatever
yes they also take up the vibrations of
those around them and they wobble around
a little bit so it's an interactive
exchange yes fundamentally it is an
exchange of information that's what
gravity is
I knew it
well congratulations I'm thinking about
this every day
and now there's another component I mean
we also have this concept we've seen
called time dilation frame dragging
objects that rotate yes planets yes well
that's very simply explain it's part of
the vibration elimination is temporal
isn't it there's a temporal well yes but
time is a side effect but if you want to
really look at it in the simplistic way
the most simplistic way possible since
you already know it's just space time
it's really one thing that has
Expressions as space and expressions as
time yes right so just look at space
time as the 100 thing look at it as a
sliding scale
if you're at this end you're
experiencing shall we say less space and
more time because you're not moving
you understand yeah but if you go to
this end you're experiencing the idea of
less time because you're occupying more
of the space
by moving
so anytime you move you're using up the
space component and not leaving enough
room for the time component and
therefore time seems to slow down
because the whole picture of SpaceTime
has to always equal 100 so if you're
occupying space 50 time has to slow down
50 because there's no room for it to be
moving at 51 if you're occupying 50 of
the Space by movement so it's really
totally just a 100 thing and depending
upon where you are in the sliding scale
determines how fast or slow or how much
you experience of space and time
[Music]